

KAMRAN SALEEM

USER EXPERIENCE/INTERFACE DESIGNER

PROFILE

UI/UX/Product/Graphic Designer with 3-years of experience in design and digital product strategy. I work with a passion for each website or application project with a strong focus on usability. I can help effectively combine business strategies and vision by meaningful, effective design and crafted solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic and UI Designer at Synergistlab

2018 - 2020

Inspiring by the principles of modernist and minimalist styles in design, my approach is simple and direct, displaying clean and functional design. My goal is to create products that balance beauty, simplicity and practicality.

Graphic and UI/UX Designer at Devbatch

2020 - 2021

I create designs for sites, landing pages, emails, logos, corporate designs, mobile app designs (with strict accordance to platform specific design guidelines). Clear naming and layering of design sources will make any developer happy.

EDUCATION

Matriculation (Science)
School Punjab public, Lahore

Intermediate (FA)

Gov college of science Year 2012 - 2014

Graduation (BA)

Virtual University Year 2015 - 2017

SOCIAL NETWORKS

- Bē https://www.behance.net/heykamransaleem
- ttps://dribbble.com/heykamransaleem
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kamran-saleem-85176a221/
- f https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100073291627177

+92 305 4579989

heykamransaleem@gmail.com

B2 Street Johar town Lahore, Pakistan

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- UI/UX Design
- Web Design
- Graphic design
- App Design
- UX Research
- Icon Design
- Logo Design

EXPERTISE

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Sketch
- Zaplin
- Prototype

HOBBIES

- Games playing
- Traveling
- Advanture
- Listening
- Reading
- Learning